{
    "id": "232668e9342f4e70b43e34411820b8fa",
    "title": "Structures with Wish | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I wish I ............................ run faster.",
            "description": "When 'wish' is used to talk about unreal or impossible situations, we use a past tense to refer to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0714ab604355496997ad5e2a276e0ab1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ............................. stay out of this.",
            "description": "When 'wish' is used to talk about unreal or impossible situations, we use a past tense to refer to the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "93f151b9d42a414480e279f3eee9ea39"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ........................ keep the volume down.",
            "description": "To express regret that things are not different, we use a past tense with wish. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "will",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32d251a026bc4009bcf288be15ecdb2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ............................... that offer.",
            "description": "Past perfect tenses are used to talk about wishes about the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "don't accept",
                "didn't accept",
                "hadn't accepted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eeee1896a840449399dfb583c7536a52"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ........................... better looking.",
            "description": "Was and were are both possible when we talk about unreal situations and conditions. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1b0dacce78d2432c96f067f3805488b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ......................... take a holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7075b5742896471ea4ddcb53a0768af2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't you wish you ........................... fly?",
            "description": "After wish, we use could to talk about wishes that we cannot realize. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e2a9de4546c44223a12f46615c5aacfb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish ........................... a table.",
            "description": "Wish + to-infinitive means want. ",
            "answers": [
                "reserve",
                "to reserve",
                "seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6d4963b7f5941529361af4aa91547e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you wish .......................... drinks on the terrace?",
            "description": "After wish, we can use an object + to-infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "I to serve",
                "me to serve",
                "me serving",
                "me serve"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39defd75dae6448ab3001a74f59ee3bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................... an appointment with the manager.",
            "description": "Wish + direct object is not normally possible without a following infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "wish",
                "want",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3b7f7e65c556465b886d8cfa02f66483"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .......................... you feel better tomorrow.",
            "description": "Wish + that-clause is not generally used for wishes about things that seem possible in the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "hope",
                "wish",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f443ce42da27485fb9a24e5e00862baf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Now I wish I ................................ to university.",
            "description": "Past perfect tenses are used for wishes about the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "go",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "98c18fe6aee345e090d671887be647c8"
        }
    ]
}